<?xml version="1.0" encoding="WINDOWS-1252"?>
<output>
<S><ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page needs to be seen to be believed <URL>yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>
<S>RT @sdlatham: The polls open in 12 hours for the <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> 2010 General Election #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Vote <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> today! #ge2010</S>
<S>Fuck <PERSON>GB</PERSON> being awarded stateman of the year, <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> is <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>! <ORGANIZATION>The Sun</ORGANIZATION> said so! #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>@TheCornishDem RT @SNPofficial @SNPTacticVoting @CallumQuinn @_SimonArnoldme Good luck <ORGANIZATION>SNP</ORGANIZATION> for tomorrow. #ge2010</S> 
<S>1st most popular issue today: Community with 13.1% of the Vote. <URL>http://is.gd/bLmFP</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S>
<S>Expected Declaration times for #ge2010 <URL>http://election.pressassociation.com/Declaration_times/general_by_time.php</URL> for @uituit others</S>
<S><PERSON>CAROLINE PIDGEON</PERSON> FOR <LOCATION>VAUXHALL</LOCATION>! #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY>win #ge2010 #fb</S> 
<S>RT @HouseofTwits: RT @rebeccawoodhead #nowplaying <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> Raging Against the Machine #RATM #ge2010 #iagreewith<PERSON>nick</PERSON> #vote Ã¢Â™Â« http://bli ... </S> 
<S><PARTY>Tories</PARTY> need a swing of 6.9% from <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> to win a majority - greater than any election since 1950. Help <PERSON>Clegg</PERSON> take lab seats instead! #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> says <PERSON>Elvis</PERSON> is alive <URL>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E-uokKdI7Kc</URL> #GE2010 # <ORGANIZATION>Labour</ORGANIZATION> #GE10 #resurrection</S> 
<S>BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <ORGANIZATION>BNP</ORGANIZATION> 2moro  <URL>http://bit.ly/abb2Q0</URL></S> 
<S>@GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Mirror</ORGANIZATION> changed front page - now using <ORGANIZATION>Bullingdon Club</ORGANIZATION> pic <URL>http://yfrog.com/5mu9hqj</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Just had a minor breakdown thinking about a <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> government (not to be confused with a miner breakdown - that was in the 80s). #ge2010</S>
<S>Awesome video <URL>http://bit.ly/bd8aGK</URL> please RT widely today. #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @WillTovey: Do the right thing tomorrow, #votepirate #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Mirror</ORGANIZATION> changed front page - now using <ORGANIZATION>Bullingdon Club</ORGANIZATION> pic <URL>http://yfrog.com/5mu9hqj</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Why is no one scared about the fact that <PERSON>George Osborne</PERSON> could be running the treasury tomorrow? #leadersdebate    #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Mirror</ORGANIZATION> changed front page - now using <ORGANIZATION>Bullingdon Club</ORGANIZATION> pic <URL>http://yfrog.com/5mu9hqj</URL> #ge2010</S>
<S><PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> making last minute address to his supporters <URL>http://tinyurl.com/32uxgef</URL> #libdem #ge2010 #ge10</S> 
<S>RT @DrJasonAbbott: #ge2010 #ge10 #labour <URL>http://twitpic.com/1lcxad</URL> <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front cover redone #ukelection #Ge2010 #Ge10 #UKelection #Ge</S> 
<S>CLASS WAR: <ORGANIZATION>Mirror</ORGANIZATION> changed front page - using THE <ORGANIZATION>Bullingdon Club</ORGANIZATION> pic! <URL>http://yfrog.com/5mu9hqj</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @dnotice: RT @sunny_hundal @political_cream: #<ORGANIZATION>theSun</ORGANIZATION> frontpage template for any parody <URL>http://twitpic.com/1ld6vx</URL> #ge2010 #disobeymurd ... </S> 
<S>RT @itsWatty: Worrying thought, if the <PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY> win the election does that mean <PERSON>Jim Davidson</PERSON> will come back to the <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION>? #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: <ORGANIZATION>The Mirror</ORGANIZATION> front page, on the otherhand, is incredulous <URL>http://yfrog.com/1rry3fj</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Why Jewish people ought not to vote for the <PARTY>LibDems</PARTY> - <URL>http://tinyurl.com/39qb8ad</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>"LetÃ¢Â€Â™s march for justice, dignity, fairness. ThatÃ¢Â€Â™s what weÃ¢Â€Â™ve all got to march for, and letÃ¢Â€Â™s march for it together" <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Best of luck today to @Lucianaberger and @Stephentwigg and the rest of you candidates! #ge2010. </S> 
<S>RT @marc_vallee: Good Night, and Good Luck, <URL>http://bit.ly/rl99C</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Why young people in <LOCATION>Swindon</LOCATION> should vote <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> | <LOCATION>Swindon</LOCATION> <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> <URL>http://ht.ly/1HvMJ</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #ge10 #<PARTY>conservatives</PARTY> #<PARTY>liberal</PARTY> #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY></S> 
<S>RT @trustgb: RT @UKelection2010: <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> addresses a late night rally in <LOCATION>Scotland</LOCATION> - the final campaign event of #ge2010 #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY></S> 
<S>#GE2010 on <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION>: <PERSON>Clegg</PERSON> was "more disarming than a <ORGANIZATION>UN</ORGANIZATION> peace force", but then became man at dinner parties "who puts the bore into <LOCATION>Bordeaux</LOCATION>" :) </S> 
<S>How will you vote tomorrow? <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> - no change, <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY> - no change, <PARTY>Conservative</PARTY> - the chance to make this country good again! #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @carlmaxim If this man decides the election will the last person to leave <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION> please turn out the lights  <URL>http://ow.ly/1HvG6</URL>  #Ge2010</S> 
<S>wonder what the environmental impact is of all the crap the main parties pushed through doors over the last few weeks! #ge2010</S> 
<S>Sell your party to me please people #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>@GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes <ORGANIZATION>The Mirror</ORGANIZATION> front page is incredulous <URL>http://yfrog.com/1rry3fj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S><ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page was really funny but upsetting, thanks @fabsass for sharing: <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Of course, all the time I should have spent on that has been well-used for #<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> #Ge2010</S>  
<S>Today is polling day for the General Election and local councils. Please use your vote. Polling stations open 7.00am to 10.00pm #GE2010</S>  
<S>Its time for normality and for the saltire to fly at the <ORGANIZATION>United Nations</ORGANIZATION> for <LOCATION>Scotland</LOCATION>. #<LOCATION>scotland</LOCATION>speaks #ge2010 #ukelections #vote<PARTY>snp</PARTY></S>  
<S>RT @guideguardian: RT @Busfield: This is better... RT @JonathanHaynes <ORGANIZATION>The Mirror</ORGANIZATION> front page is incredulous <URL>http://yfrog.com/1rry3fj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @samwolfson: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S><URL>http://twitter.com/AmandaJConroy/statuses/13451794833</URL> <ORGANIZATION>Nazis</ORGANIZATION> did same on way to power. They wanted thugs to join #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>I have decided who I will vote for tomorrow.. who wins is besides the point.. whoever it is I hope they keep promise.. at the end #ge2010</S>  
<S>Watching the #ge2010 results tomorrow? Stay up all night with <URL>BusinessZone.co.uk</URL>! <URL>http://ow.ly/1Hnty</URL> #ukelection</S>  
<S>@huwspanner How about <PERSON>Vince Cable</PERSON> for Chancellor? #ge2010 #ge10</S>  
<S>RT @lucus_: what the <ORGANIZATION>suns</ORGANIZATION> front page SHOULD read tomorrow | <URL>http://cl.ly/oxr</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>1st Today with 8.7% of Votes: " Provide family learning courses in every county,..." <URL>http://is.gd/buCja</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>A fair number of <ORGANIZATION>Americans</ORGANIZATION> in my <ORGANIZATION>twitter</ORGANIZATION> stream but hardly  a mention of #ukelection #ge2010 from any of them. Have they even noticed? </S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>i reckon tomorrow is official buy a copy of the <ORGANIZATION>sun</ORGANIZATION> and rip it up on the counter day #ukelection #ge2010 #rip<ORGANIZATION>sun</ORGANIZATION></S>  
<S>RT @robertsoftley: BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2moro  <URL>http://bit</URL>. ... </S>  
<S><PERSON>Mrs Mac</PERSON> is judging who she votes for based on their haircut! #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @jordandias: Would rather have <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> as PM than <PERSON>Brown</PERSON>.  #fact #ukelection #ge2010</S>  
<S>How does anyone take the <ORGANIZATION>Mail</ORGANIZATION> seriously when their website is plastered with celebrity gossip? #GE2010 #<PARTY>tory</PARTY>twats</S>  
<S>RT @allriffnoraff: Apparently "He [<PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON>] can fix the country given enough time." Exactly how much time does he need? #ge2010</S>  
<S>My <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> general election quiz results at <URL>http://whoshouldyouvotefor.com</URL>: <PARTY>UKIP</PARTY>+18 <PARTY>LAB</PARTY>+18 <PARTY>CON</PARTY>0 <URL>http://wsyvf.com/uk/6tXK0TI03wbi0n0b</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @tothecommons: RT @jmcsmith: Naked man seen running towards <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> Parliament... <URL>http://bit.ly/aMxMj9</URL>  #youreit #tothecommons #ge2010 #ta ... </S>
<S>Unite members begin 24 hour stoppage at <ORGANIZATION> Glasgow Herald</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION> The Evening Times</ORGANIZATION> <URL>http://bit.ly/9yp0cr</URL>  #<LOCATION>scotland</LOCATION>speaks #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @twitVoteUK: Current result:1st <PARTY>Liberal Democrat Party</PARTY>  with 65.6% See <URL>www.twitVoteUK.org.uk</URL> for more info #twitVoteUK #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>@iaindale There will be cross-party consensus on this being the most bizarre moment in Campaign 2010: <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @twitVoteUK: The leading party in our poll has changed in <LOCATION>HOVE</LOCATION>, and is now the <PARTY>Liberal Democrat Party</PARTY>  #ge2010</S>  
<S>Well worth a watch #ge2010  RT @Andy_Parsons: This is very amusing and apt . <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> - The Common People <URL>http://goo.gl/PtBU</URL></S>  
<S>RT @PaulPunktastic: RT @tmjackson: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 (via @aylott)</S>  
<S>RT @aylott RT @tmjackson: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @YoungLabourite: The day <ORGANIZATION>The Sun</ORGANIZATION> lost all creadibility - an insult to President <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> : <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL>  #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @Busfield RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Fancy a free Ã‚Â£25 bet on the election with <ORGANIZATION>Betfair</ORGANIZATION>? <URL>http://bit.ly/bR4Hi5</URL> #GE2010</S>  
<S>This is the first time I have been undecided who to vote for. My heart is saying one thing, my head is saying another. #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @robinbogg OK I have seen <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> cover now. Astonishing. Almsot #beyondparody but give me time. #evenstalinwouldturninhisgrave #ge2010 #ge10</S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 /via @martingoode</S>  
<S>murdoch tabloid steals <PERSON>obama</PERSON> poster motif to promote <PARTY>conservative</PARTY> candidate in british election <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @UKLabourParty: #imnotvotingconservative because <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> and <PERSON>Osborne</PERSON> are Clones of <PERSON>Thatcher</PERSON> #GE2010</S>  
<S>RT @mjrobbins: RT @dnotice: Ooh! A list of when each #ukelection seat (should) be called <URL>http://is.gd/bVUQb</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @mjrobbins: RT @dnotice: Ooh! A list of when each #ukelection seat (should) be called <URL>http://is.gd/bVUQb</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Gotta love the <ORGANIZATION>Mirror</ORGANIZATION> front page: <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>: Prime Minister? Really? #ge2010</S>  
<S>Show your disgust with <ORGANIZATION>Youtube</ORGANIZATION> selling out the the <PARTY>tories</PARTY> and delete your <ORGANIZATION>youtube</ORGANIZATION> account. #ukelection #<PERSON>philipastroud</PERSON> #gonick #ge2010</S>  
<S>Trending Today: "Everyone should be treated equally in life no matter their race,..." <URL>http://is.gd/btwQG</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>RT @AndrewHerts: @vote_tory <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> deregulated the Banks and crashed the <LOCATION>uk</LOCATION>. Dont vote them back! #vote<PARTY>tory</PARTY> #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>RT @sachab loving the new-found hatred of the <PERSON>Murdoch</PERSON> press on <ORGANIZATION> twitter</ORGANIZATION>  perhaps there was no <ORGANIZATION> Twitter</ORGANIZATION> at the last election? #ge2010</S>  
<S>Do <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> really think Posh Boy is <PERSON>Obama</PERSON>? <URL>http://bit.ly/bZv7cl</URL> RT @JonathanHaynes <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page: WOW <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @Miss_Lucifer: The Scum... RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>"The Burning Issue For <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>?" , #<ORGANIZATION>DailyMail</ORGANIZATION>? To burn as many copies of your vile rag as humanly possible! #Newsnight #GE2010</S>  
<S>RT @aylott: RT @tmjackson: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 (via @GdnPolitics) Couv <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> demain!!</S>  
<S>#ge2010 There really is something seriously unsettling about <PERSON>Mandy</PERSON> :)</S>  
<S>RT @ruththetruth RT @keelingoverkaz: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>be very fucking afraid. vote <PARTY>labour</PARTY> ;) RT @guardiannews <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> eyes the prize as polls suggest <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> victory <URL>http://bit.ly/cuFR0J</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Rather depressed about how few of my <ORGANIZATION>Twitter</ORGANIZATION> cohort have even mentioned the election #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @gabrielmilland: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> splash.... wow. But not in a good way. <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 via @little_wing123</S>  
<S>Ah, our good old UK media. #ge2010 Check out <ORGANIZATION>The Sun</ORGANIZATION>. What fucking scumbags. <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL></S>  
<S>Watch the <PERSON>Sir Stuart Bell</PERSON> - <PERSON>Joan McTigue</PERSON> #Postergate video here. Five more years of this man as MP? <URL>http://bit.ly/bBoV5L</URL> #GE2010</S>  
<S>This is a bit much. RT @JonathanHaynes <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 (via @johnestevens)</S>  
<S>RT @libby_brooks: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 > Christ</S>  
<S><LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> election day tomorrow!!  #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @TeamPangloss: <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> is winning on passion, <PERSON>Clegg</PERSON> is winning on facts, <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> is winning on tan. #LeadersDebate #GE2010</S>  
<S>BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2m ...</S>  
<S>RT @jedhallam: Disgraceful footage of <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> stamping on young guys head <URL>http://bit.ly/cAgEgP</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @markcreaser: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @edfordham: Last interview of the pre-voting campaign: <PERSON>Ed Fordham</PERSON> <URL>http://bit.ly/ci0Qdg</URL>  #GE2010</S>  
<S>RT @libby_brooks: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 Holy FUCK. </S>  
<S>RT @Labour_Can_Win This article needs to get to as many people as possible TONIGHT. RT <URL>http://bit.ly/dzxwiv</URL> #GE2010 #UKElection</S>  
<S>RT @fiddlecub: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010. </S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010 > Christ</S>  
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: #<ORGANIZATION>theSun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://bit.ly/bssUzR</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>So tomorrow is the big day. No matter the outcome, it should sure be an interesting day. #ge2010</S>  
<S>LOL RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Vote Yellow TOMORROW! Retweet for hope! <URL>http://bit.ly/cP74x9</URL> #ukelection #libdems #ge2010 #newsnight</S>  
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S><PERSON>Kol Tregaskes</PERSON>: <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> News - Election 2010: Leaders make final bid for votes #ge10 #ge2010:  <URL>http://bit.ly/c35QfG</URL> </S>  
<S>just been listening to my old Politics lecturer, the legend <PERSON>JT</PERSON>, on <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> 5 Live talking #ge2010,on my phone,in the Everyman, for <PERSON>Bills</PERSON> Bday</S>  
<S>Is tonight like the Evil Twin of Christmas Eve? #ge2010</S>  
<S>A bit dramatic... <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @kirkleesunity: BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2moro  <URL>http://bit</URL>. ...</S>  
<S>Who should I vote for? My results at <URL>http://whoshouldyouvotefor.com</URL>: <PARTY>CON</PARTY>+57 <PARTY>LAB</PARTY>+7 <PARTY>UKIP</PARTY>+5 <URL>http://wsyvf.com/sc/18Hle9g1b0HQyKMjQ</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S>  
<S>Nice! RT @GdnPolitics: RT @JonathanHaynes: WOW: <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION> front page - has to be seen to be believed! <URL>http://yfrog.com/jncm8hj</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Oh god, the <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> has a CGI <LOCATION>Downing Street</LOCATION> with animated constituency-named paving stones leading to No. 10. #ukelection #newsnight #ge2010</S>  
<S>2nd Today with 1.0% of Votes: " Stop <ORGANIZATION>NHS</ORGANIZATION>  funding  for therapies like homeopathy..." <URL>http://is.gd/bP9QK</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>RT @stonecypher: BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2moro  <URL>http://bit.ly</URL> ...</S>  
<S>BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2moro <URL>http://bit.ly/abb2Q0</URL> #fb</S>  
<S>It is projected that VAT will rise to at least 19% in Jan 2011 under a <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> government (<URL>http://bit.ly/9cI9yJ</URL>). #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY> #ge2010</S>  
<S>"Good point, well made" = <URL>http://twitpic.com/1lcleu</URL> ~ Incisive political commentary ~ #<PERSON>DavidCameron</PERSON> #<PERSON>GordonBrown</PERSON> #GE2010 (RT @td_ward</S>) 
<S>Trending Today: " Invest heavily in renewable energy. Without energy hospitals,..." <URL>http://is.gd/bPZaz</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>RT Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthe<PARTY>bnp</PARTY> #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2moro  <URL>http://bit.ly</URL>  ...</S>  
<S>RT @Sketchybear: So <PERSON>Mugabe</PERSON>  is backing <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>. Was THAT the black man he met the other week..? #ge2010</S>  
<S># <LOCATION>Warrington South</LOCATION> in 100 key seats Help #KeepToriesOut. See- <URL>http://bit.ly/deKwGu</URL> (Rank 21) #<LOCATION>Cheshire</LOCATION> #ukelection #ge2010. Please ReTweet</S>  
<S> <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> has by far the most glamorous wife of the 3 candidates #WAGs #ge2010 #jenesaisquoi #ukelection #<PERSON>miriamgonzalezdurantez</PERSON></S>  
<S>Pass this image around and make people know they can keep <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> out of <LOCATION>Downing St</LOCATION>! #ge2010 <URL>http://twitpic.com/1lcmiz</URL></S>  
<S>New 8% lead for <PARTY>Tories</PARTY>. Latest <ORGANIZATION>Guardian</ORGANIZATION>/<ORGANIZATION>ICM</ORGANIZATION> poll results - plus new trend data #ge2010 http://bit.ly/d1o0XQ</S>  
<S>Having a quick drink in the local club, not long to go, busy 24 hours ahead, #GE2010 #gameon</S>  
<S>RT @electionpredict: JUST OUT: <ORGANIZATION>ComRes</ORGANIZATION> poll puts <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> 9 points ahead <URL>http://bit.ly/aWEOWJ</URL> #GE2010</S>  
<S>@Labour_Can_Win: 4 Over 44,000 more doctors #GE2010 #AFutureFairForAll #YouCantTouchThis  #ThankYou<PARTY>Labour</PARTY></S>  
<S>Twenty two million people are benefiting from real tax cuts to boost their income this year #YouCantTouchThis #GE2010  #ThankYou<PARTY>Labour</PARTY></S>  
<S>@jon_sayers I fear that too, and hope that people realise the danger. #keep<PARTY>tories</PARTY>out #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @electionpredict JUST OUT: <ORGANIZATION>ComRes</ORGANIZATION> poll puts <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> 9 points ahead <URL>http://bit.ly/aWEOWJ</URL> #GE2010</S>  
<S>4 Over 44,000 more doctors #GE2010 #AFutureFairForAll #YouCantTouchThis  #ThankYou<PARTY>Labour</PARTY></S>  
<S>Tonight we must dance for tomorrow we may face conservatism. #ge2010</S>  
<S>@LisaTalkingTots Urr, gonna be stuck in front of the TV - always been an election night saddo #ge2010</S>  
<S><PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthe<PARTY>bnp</PARTY> #ge2010 <URL>http://bit.ly/abb2Q0</URL> </S>  
<S>RT @WNIPT: ALL <PARTY>LIB DEM</PARTY> FANS MAKE SURE YOU BLOODY WELL VOTE TOMORROW. DO IT FIRST THING. RT THIS.#ge2010 #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud</PERSON> #ukelection #<PARTY>Lib</PARTY> ...</S>  
<S>Meeting @brixtonalex bright and early, election day is almost here. Bring it on. #ge2010 #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY></S>  
<S>For the love of all that is good and decent in this world, VOTE <PARTY>LIB DEM</PARTY>!!!!!!! #ge2010 #ukelection #go<PERSON>Nick</PERSON></S>  
<S>BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> 2moro  <URL>http://bit.ly/abb2Q0</URL></S>  
<S>Looking forward to spitting out my vote tomorrow! #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @Lilly1690: RT @eddieishere <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> National News ignoring NI again... The night before the election. #ge2010 #<ORGANIZATION>bbc</ORGANIZATION> #<ORGANIZATION>bbc</ORGANIZATION>fail no c ... </S>  
<S><LOCATION>Monte Carlo</LOCATION> Forecast analysis of Harris 6/5: <PARTY>CON</PARTY>: 308-329, <PARTY>LAB</PARTY>: 224-243, <PARTY>LD</PARTY>: 66-81 Forecast: HUNG to <PARTY>CON</PARTY>+<PARTY>DUP</PARTY> pact #ge2010 #ukelection #ge10</S>  
<S>I heard that <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> shoots gays, gingers and single mothers on sight. #ge2010 #ukelection /via @AnthonyMaxwell and <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> eats them</S>  
<S><ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> National News ignoring NI again... The night before the election. #ge2010 #<ORGANIZATION>bbc</ORGANIZATION> #<ORGANIZATION>bbc</ORGANIZATION>fail</S>  
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.12 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI</S>  
<S>General Election 2010: <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> urges public to choose hope over fear <URL>http://tgr.ph/a6jIbK</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>GeneralElection biscuits. Turned out a bit iffy red ones kept collapsing. An allegory of things to come? #ge2010 <URL>http://twitpic.com/1lch08</URL></S>  
<S>RT @laurenm: BREAKING Ã¢Â€Â“ <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leader in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION> kicks bloodied man in head. #stopthebnp #ge2010. You can stop <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> tomorrow <URL>http://bit.ly/a</URL> ...</S>  
<S><PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> addresses a late night rally in <LOCATION>Scotland</LOCATION> - the final campaign event of #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @TheMainstand: #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> #imnotvoting<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY> <PERSON>GB</PERSON> is the man for the job #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @VoteNoTories: #Eastbourne Help #Keep<PARTY>Tories</PARTY>Out. See- <URL>http://bit.ly/deKwGu</URL> (Rank 38) #<LOCATION>Sussex</LOCATION> #ukelection #ge2010. Please ReTweet</S>  
<S><ORGANIZATION>ITV News</ORGANIZATION> - why look to history? Try looking north of the border re hung parliaments, coalitions and minority govts. #ge2010</S>  
<S>Big day tomorrow. Do the right thing <LOCATION>Islington South</LOCATION> and elect <PERSON>@BridgetFox</PERSON> as our next MP. #ge2010</S>  
<S>surly a tactical vote is to @vote_tory! Be strategic! think long term! think revitalisation! WANT CHANGE? VOTE <PARTY>TORY</PARTY> #GE2010 #<PARTY>labour</PARTY>fail</S>  
<S><PERSON>Brown</PERSON> for substance or Blue for spin - you decide! #ukelection #ge2010 #typeofperson who wants a #<PARTY>labour</PARTY>win plz RT (rt@labourwin)</S>  
<S>RT @StunLaurel: Wonder if the <PERSON>Milliband brothers</PERSON> will be interviewed by the <PERSON>Dimbleby brothers</PERSON>?  #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>#<LOCATION>Thurrock</LOCATION>  Help #Keep<PARTY>Tories</PARTY>Out. See- <URL>http://bit.ly/deKwGu</URL> (Rank53) #<LOCATION>Essex</LOCATION>  #ukelection #ge2010. Please ReTweet</S>  
<S>VOTE <PARTY>@Conservatives</PARTY> tomorrow!! Vote for change! They need majority!! #ge2010</S>  
<S>Where did the last minute <PARTY>tory</PARTY>  bump come from, come on guys vote <PARTY>lib dem</PARTY>, or <PARTY>lab</PARTY>, or green, or someone! #ge2010 #imnotvoting<PARTY>tory</PARTY></S>  
<S><PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> - "I will not head a government". Too bloody right #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @newsnetscotland: Another leading businessmen call for Scottish fiscal autonomy <URL>http://bit.ly/azgsAj</URL> - #ge2010 #<LOCATION>scotland</LOCATION> #<LOCATION>scotland</LOCATION>spe ... </S>  
<S>is having a very early start tomorrow but looking forward to making a difference! #bmeb #Vote<PARTY>Conservative</PARTY> #GE2010 #Vote4Change</S>  
<S>@Steeluloid ~ A perfect bedtime lullaby. <URL>http://tinyurl.com/375twlf</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>Last VI of the campaign done.  Less than 6 hrs before leaflet drop + GOTV!! #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @LabourWIN: <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> for substance or Blue for spin - you decide!  #ukelection #ge2010 #typeofperson who wants a #<PARTY>labour</PARTY>win plz RT</S>  
<S>Really disappointed no one has knocked on my door to try and convince me to vote for them. Effect of the tv debate? #ge2010 </S>
<S>RT @Unionbuster: RT @bradwiggins: Just watching <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> talking fluent Dutch on telly, impressed! ,Is he standing in <LOCATION>Holland</LOCATION>? #ge2010</S>  
<S><ORGANIZATION>Guardian</ORGANIZATION>/<ORGANIZATION>ICM</ORGANIZATION> eve-of-election poll: 43% expect hung parliament <URL>http://gu.com/p/2gzx8</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>@WhiteGM 49% would vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY> if they could win (Source: <ORGANIZATION>YouGov</ORGANIZATION>)  with 49% they would - so go for it! #ukelection #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @UKelection2010: Spectator - Deceitful <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> returns to the old dividing line #ge2010 <URL>http://is.gd/bVNRR</URL></S>  
<S>How did tech do in the #GE2010 manifestos? "<PARTY>Greens</PARTY> would repeal the "flawed and illiberal" Digital Economy Act" - <URL>http://bit.ly/belw14</URL></S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: "Reform the libel laws and prevent rags like the Daily..." <URL>http://is.gd/bR0SQ</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S>  
<S>RT @filmdetail: <PERSON>Robert Mugabe</PERSON> gives <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> election backing <URL>http://bit.ly/cKdb0E</URL> #ge2010</S>  
<S>I agreed most with <PERSON>Steve Whiffen</PERSON> (<PARTY>Green Party</PARTY>) in <LOCATION>Daventry</LOCATION> - how about you? <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL> @democlub #ge2010</S>  
<S>RT @electionpredict: Betting: 59% Hung Parl, 40% <PARTY>Con</PARTY> Majority. New <ORGANIZATION>ComRes</ORGANIZATION> poll out in 12 minutes, so watch this space! #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @ivolunteeruk: NEW - Party spokespeople on charities &amp; volunteering <URL>http://bit.ly/bshsMe</URL> <URL>http://bit.ly/b532BC</URL> <URL>http://bit.ly/bZm</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @paul_turri: <URL>http://twitgoo.com/uomqg</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 a light hearted reason not to vote<PARTY>labour</PARTY> :)</S> 
<S>RT @RockTheVoteNow RT @hare_wood: All the reasons you need never to vote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY>:  <PERSON>Will Hutton</PERSON>: <URL>http://bit.ly/b3M1a8</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #ge10</S> 
<S>RT @hare_wood: All the reasons you need never to vote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY>:  <PERSON>Will Hutton</PERSON>: <URL>http://bit.ly/b3M1a8</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #ge10 #imnotvoting<PARTY>con</PARTY> ...</S> 
<S>@LichfieldGE2010  Well, we could pray for a hung parliament followed by another general election. Or just get a new hobby! #GE2010</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: "Make IVF free (not just 1 attempt!) for all working..." <URL>http://is.gd/bp96x</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>#ukelection #ge2010 <PERSON>Amanda Patel</PERSON> so full of shit - bbccampaignshow</S> 
<S>RT @prestolee: Predicted declaration times  <URL>http://bit.ly/bafsuk</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Just remember, it all comes down to you and an X. People have and would die for that right. DONT waste it. Think before you vote! #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @hare_wood: All the reasons you need never to vote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY>:  <PERSON>Will Hutton</PERSON>: <URL>http://bit.ly/b3M1a8</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #ge10 #imnotvoting<PARTY>con</PARTY> ...</S> 
<S>friday weather: cold, northeasterly winds! #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @ddbanks: The <PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY> to win the <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> general election with a majority of 27. You heard it here first #leadersdebate #GE2010</S> 
<S>Election 2010: a bracing reminder of the price we pay for political freedom <URL>http://tgr.ph/90GNQl</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Where I live people have the power of 0.73 votes. See how much your vote is worth at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI #ukelections</S> 
<S>@OyeBilly @samaryd ha! yes, <ORGANIZATION>Watneys Red Barrel</ORGANIZATION> prob more appropriate for <PARTY>BNP</PARTY>. #electiondrinkinggame #electionparty #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @ukpolitico the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> will win clear majority, but of less than ten seats. #ukelection #ge10 #ge2010 // agreed ... been saying 10 seats</S> 
<S>RT @angelneptustar: If you love <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>, vote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY>.      #ge2010  #election2010   #bigotgate  #ge10</S> 
<S>RT @ukpolitico: My prediction is that the <PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY> will win a clear majority, but of less than ten seats. #ukelection #ge10 #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @restyrestall: Well, the politics has well and truly kicked off on <ORGANIZATION>Facebook</ORGANIZATION> this evening! #voteforchange #ge2010 #imvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY></S> 
<S>I really appreciated this article : <URL>http://twurl.nl/yvbmto</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>May as well fire up the hashtag #LibDemLandslide, warm it up in anticipation for #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @blogpreston: the election in <LOCATION>preston</LOCATION> + surrounding constituencies in figures: <URL>http://bit.ly/cC2j9Y</URL> #<LOCATION>preston</LOCATION>10 #ge2010</S> 
<S>#ge2010 Times using Populus poll (and not <ORGANIZATION>Yougov</ORGANIZATION> in the <ORGANIZATION>Sun</ORGANIZATION>) is effectively calling the election for the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> already!!!!</S> 
<S>Any one care to predict how many Cabinet ministers will loose their seats? #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @kelfenton: #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> because the <PARTY>Lib Dems</PARTY> have much better policies, and I like foxes and the gays.  #ge2010 #leaders ...</S> 
<S>@sjzara This is why it matters  <PERSON>David Stroud</PERSON> signs Xian extremist declaration <URL>http://bit.ly/cccgEl</URL> #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud</PERSON> #ge2010 #election2010</S> 
<S>#ukelection #ge2010 #<PARTY>tory</PARTY>fail after flop of <PERSON>camerons</PERSON> big society idea - what have the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> got left - NOTHING</S> 
<S><PERSON>Jackie Ashley</PERSON> says dissent at <ORGANIZATION>Guardian</ORGANIZATION> re support for <PARTY>lib dems</PARTY> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>@Angelneptustar  <PERSON>David Stroud</PERSON> signs Xian extremist declaration <URL>http://bit.ly/cccgEl</URL> #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud</PERSON> #ge2010 #election2010  #Toryfail</S> 
<S>Latest tracker poll suggests <PARTY>Torys</PARTY> only 11 seats ahead of <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> on current predictions. Tight!! #GE2010 #UKElection</S> 
<S>RT @Ian_Fraser: <PERSON>George Osborn</PERSON> privately sucks up to #bankers he publicly bashes #ge2010 <URL>http://bit.ly/dA3vK1</URL> <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> not to be tr ...</S> 
<S>The road to <LOCATION>Downing Street</LOCATION> <URL>http://bit.ly/bAmAKP</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @bilbobaggins2k: Every time <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> looks like he might win, the volcano gets angry....Just saying. #ge2010  #<PERSON>nickcleggs</PERSON>fault</S> 
<S>RT @AndyMesa: Thinking of voting for <PARTY>Labour</PARTY>? Think again, 13 years of disappointment &amp; scandal <URL>http://ht.ly/1GWpB</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S><PARTY>LibDems</PARTY>, do not disappoint come Friday. Form the coalition with the right party #ImVoting<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> #ge2010 /via (cont) <URL>http://tl.gd/15o2qq</URL></S> 
<S>Seriously tweeps, the thought of a <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> government on Friday makes me want to throw myself down the stairs... #ge2010 #<PARTY>Tory</PARTY>Homophobes</S> 
<S>RT @captaink99: BIGOT = <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> Is Going On Thursday.  #ge2010 #ukelection > LOL</S> 
<S>VOTE <PARTY>LABOUR</PARTY>!  RT @MatthewEyre: <PERSON>Richard Littlejohn</PERSON> is threatening to emigrate permanently if <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> or the <PARTY>Lib Dems</PARTY> win. #ge2010</S> 
<S>The draw back to a hung parliament exists only in the minds of <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> who want absolute rule. #<PARTY>tory</PARTY>fail #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @HouseofTwits RT @eljmayes <PERSON>Angus Reid</PERSON>/Political Betting Poll- <PARTY>CON</PARTY> 36 <PARTY>LIB DEM</PARTY> 29 <PARTY>LAB</PARTY> 24 #GE2010</S> 
<S>"Were in this together" means the poor should pay the same share as the rich that got us in this mess. #<PARTY>tory</PARTY>fail #ge2010</S> 
<S>BIGOT = <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> Is Going On Thursday.  #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>#<LOCATION>Luton North</LOCATION> Help #KeepToriesOut. See- <URL>http://bit.ly/deKwGu</URL> (Rank 44) #<LOCATION>Bedfordshire</LOCATION>  #ukelection #ge2010. Please ReTweet</S> 
<S>Election Party Pack .. you know you want to!!  <URL>http://bit.ly/9VlArc</URL>  #ge2010  #ukelection</S>  
<S>RT @Ajouk So with <ORGANIZATION>Yougov</ORGANIZATION> showing the <PARTY>Lib Dems</PARTY> back in the race, I assume we will hear no more about them being squeezed #ge2010</S>  
<S>Election Special: Copyright and illegal downloading. <URL>http://is.gd/bVM1H</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection #votepirate</S>  
<S>Omg what is <PERSON>@RealBillBailey</PERSON> doing in a #<PARTY>labour</PARTY> advert ? Sometimes peoples voting choices seem so wrong ! #ge2010</S>  
<S>@RaacheLeach  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S>  
<S>@iman4d  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S>  
<S>@Megfdavies  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S>  
<S>RT @JeremyJHardy In <LOCATION>Henley on Thames</LOCATION>, vote <PERSON>Sinn Fein</PERSON>. #ge2010</S>  
<S>@jenimartian  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S>  
<S>@damopk1  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S>  
<S>RT @Jordeejord: Stocking up on candles and tinned food. Survival gear ready in case the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> get in :(</S>
<S><PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> are fucking retarded. Fuck off you stupid facist cunts. #ge2010</S>  
<S>If you are in <LOCATION>Oxford</LOCATION>, here is where you find your polling station <URL>http://bit.ly/anblWv</URL> <LOCATION>Oxford</LOCATION> council helpfully made it had to find #ge2010</S> 
<S>@bluebanana23  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S> 
<S>@chamaerops  So you want another 5 years of this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> then? #GE2010 #Voteforchange #ukelection #UKVote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> :)</S> 
<S>Stobard is #trending . Thanks, @SarahBrown10 ! #ge10 #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @twitVoteUK: Still time to vote on <URL>www.twitvoteuk.org.uk</URL> as it only takes a second with our anonymous form #ge2010 #ukelection #ukvot ...</S>
<S>RT@guardiannews Help map voting turnout tomorrow by tweeting #ukvote + 1st half of yr postcode after you vote <URL>http://gu.com/p/2gm59</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Vote - <PERSON>Harry Enfield</PERSON>, <PERSON>Captain Birdseye</PERSON> or <PERSON>Jedward</PERSON> - What a great political choice. #GE2010</S> 
<S>If theres a hung parliament I suggest a job share. The triminister? #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @robshepherd: 10pm, May 6: <PERSON>Brown</PERSON>, <PERSON>Clegg</PERSON> &amp; <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> negotiate for the keys to Number 10 <URL>http://bit.ly/4FqD</URL>  #ge2010 #ge10 #election2010</S> 
<S>RT @guardiannews Help map voting turnout tomorrow by tweeting #ukvote + 1st half of yr postcode after you vote <URL>http://gu.com/p/2gm59</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @guyhodge - Politics in todays election edition of #TheGreatIndoors comic on @gamebrit: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3xklgyj</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>Voting for one of the 3 big parties in #ge2010 is like getting to choose which bully gets to kick your head in for the next 5 years. </S> 
<S>@UKLabour #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY> because compassion and fairness will be the guiding principles in securing the recovery #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @UKLabourParty: #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> because they want to control peoples thinking through their <PERSON>Murdoch</PERSON> media #<ORGANIZATION>SkyNews</ORGANIZATION> #GE2010 RT</S> 
<S>RT @SirBlimelyWindy: Mr <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>, the reason you think society is broken is cos the <PARTY>tories</PARTY> destroyed it before and it takes time #ge2010  ...</S> 
<S>RT @MinaCab: RT @carlmaxim: Every time <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> looks like he might win the volcano gets angry....Just saying. #ge2010 #ukelection lol</S> 
<S>Is this true: By law a defaced ballot has to be placed in a separate pile to check if a box was ticked (if so it has to be honored) #GE2010</S> 
<S>@MrsP2003 Well apparently 32% of #<LOCATION>Stirling</LOCATION> want 5 more years of <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> :( &amp; this: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y43bsu</URL> #GE2010 #UKvote And 29% of <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION></S> 
<S>RT @CameronForPM: Polls Open in less than 11 Hours. Vote For Change - Vote <PARTY>Conservative</PARTY> #GE2010 #UKElection</S> 
<S>RT @dirkvl: Why Endorse The <PARTY>Tories</PARTY>? ... ItÃ¢Â€Â™s utterly bizarre- <PERSON>Paul Krugman</PERSON> <URL>http://tinyurl.com/282r5nd</URL> #GE2010 @evanhd >he would vote <PARTY>LibDem</PARTY></S> 
<S>"My vote is worth 0.06 votes".  What a load of bullshit.  Your vote is worth 1 vote.  Use it well, for who YOU want. #Election #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @ppinternational: RT @PiratePartyUK: 12 hours until polls open. 12 hours until you can vote for your rights. #votepirate #ge2010... </S> 
<S>No <PERSON>ordon</PERSON>, your 1st priority is keeping your grubby little hands on power &amp; your desperate regime in Government! #GE2010</S> 
<S>#DC10 #TomorrowForChange #GE2010</S> 
<S>Had a handful of people at work asking me how they should vote, and not understanding FPTP system. I despair, I really do #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> = big society. <PERSON>Thatcher</PERSON> = no such thing as society. Ergo, <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> = one big nothing? #ge2010</S> 
<S>#imvotinglabour because <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> says <PERSON>Elvis Presley</PERSON> is alive and supporting him. <URL>http://tinyurl.com/35j8qul</URL> Miracles can happen. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Politics and lolitics in an election edition of <ORGANIZATION>The Great Indoors</ORGANIZATION> comic today on @gamebrit: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3xklgyj</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>What are they shouting at <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON>?? #ge2010</S> 
<S>Of course, if you live in <LOCATION>Brentford</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Isleworth</LOCATION> then go <PARTY>Lib-Dem</PARTY> and vote @andrewdakers if I can change, so can you! #GE2010</S>
<S>Hey Hey! RT @gracefreeman: <PERSON>Cleggy</PERSON>! <URL>http://twitpic.com/1lbi7u</URL> #ge2010 #<LOCATION>sheffield</LOCATION></S> 
<S>likes "<LOCATION>Birmingham Edgbaston</LOCATION>" declaration time 0:45 <URL>http://bit.ly/cr7sQs</URL>  now thats planning #ge2010</S> 
<S>After 18 years of <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> rule followed by 13 years of New <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> we desperately need a change for the better. Vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY>. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Times/Populus poll puts <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> within inches of victory: <URL>http://bit.ly/a1amNj</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @guardiannews: Help map voting turnout Thurs by tweeting #ukvote + 1st half of yr postcode after you vote <URL>http://gu.com/p/2gm59</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Crazy <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> lady from crazy ultra-patriarchal church objects to people pointing out her hating on teh gay <URL>http://bit.ly/9dM5Is</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @rebelmole: Latest polls still firmly in hung parl land: <URL>http://ukpollingreport.co.uk/blog/archives/2683</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>Thanks to <PARTY>Labour</PARTY>, we now live in a society where pizza gets to your house before the police. #<PARTY>labourfail</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Will there be a Grand Rolling Up of Sleeves Ceremony alongside a <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> Queens Speech? #ge2010 #<PARTY>libdems</PARTY></S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>Only a few hours left to add your vote to <URL>www.twitvoteuk.org.uk</URL> and to view our map. Thanks to all who have done so. Please RT #ge2010 #ge10</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.1 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI &gt;---sod all then</S> 
<S><ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> Expose <LOCATION>Stroud</LOCATION> Dogging <URL>http://bit.ly/ax8Gfq</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection  #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY>majority</S> 
<S>I now hope <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> gets in. It will give many of us someone to bitch and moan about for the next 5 years. #ge2010</S> 
<S>ooh, @krishgm has got his swingometer out... #ge2010</S> 
<S>HAHAHAAAA! A lady on the telly said she was voting for <PERSON>Dave</PERSON> cos of his policies! Funny laydee #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @retrophunk84: #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> because #iagreewithnick and am voting #<PARTY>libdems</PARTY> in the #ukelection #ge2010 which is of course  ...</S> 
<S>@itsalovelycake RT @paulbradshaw In free market, with 2 political parties selling Change, will that drive the price of Change down? #ge2010</S> 
<S>Is <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> <PERSON>Neil Kinnock</PERSON> in disguise, with his foot in his mouth, the only unelected leader not to win an election #ge2010</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: "more poker and hookers!" <URL>http://is.gd/blI8L</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>In a free market, with 2 political parties selling Change, will that drive the price of Change down? #ge2010</S> 
<S>Thank goodness we have a free and impartial press to tell me how to vote. They must think I am too stupid to make up my own mind. #ge2010</S> 
<S>just downloaded the Election 2010 app #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Who should I vote for? My results at <URL>http://whoshouldyouvotefor.com</URL>: <PARTY>LAB</PARTY>+20 <PARTY>CON</PARTY>+6 <PARTY>UKIP</PARTY>+3 <URL>http://wsyvf.com/uk/73NnMFjXFl7okNcD</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @democlub: Want to see responses to our survey grouped by party?  Rough and ready data online at <URL>http://bit.ly/bEsDuT</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>I agreed most with <PERSON>Mike Plummer</PERSON> (<PARTY>Liberal Democrats</PARTY>) in <LOCATION>New Forest West</LOCATION> - how about you? <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL> @democlub #ge2010 #NForestW</S> 
<S>In order for favourites #<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> to be unseated, they needs to be a 13.8% swing in voters. #<LOCATION>Preston</LOCATION>10 #ge2010</S>
<S>I am going to miss you guys when this is over!!    #ge2010 #leadersdebate</S> 
<S>RT @PiratePartyUK: 12 hours until polls open. 12 hours until you can vote for your rights. #vote<PARTY>pirate</PARTY> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Haha <PERSON>nick clegg</PERSON> (or clogg as the woman on channel 4 news said) arriving to a chorus of boos in <LOCATION>Durham</LOCATION>! #vote<PARTY>labour</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>12 hours to go now for the #ukelection, you guys. #ge10 #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @PiratePartyUK: 12 hours until polls open. 12 hours until you can vote for your rights. #vote<PARTY>pirate</PARTY> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>haha yellow barriers for the yellow rally #<ORGANIZATION>channel4news</ORGANIZATION> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Great site to match which party and candidate you align best with  on issues <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL>  #GE10  #ge2010 #UKElection</S>
<S>RT @plinth_man: <PERSON>Mandelson</PERSON> has a dream -  the next queen of <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> #ge2010 #ukelection//To have a Brazilian. Oh, hang on.. .</S> 
<S>RT @faithjegede The night before the end of New <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> as we know it. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Schhhh... so this what a Hung parliament looks like. <URL>http://twitgoo.com/uof8g</URL> #election #ge2010</S> 
<S>2 words to remind you to vote <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> - <PERSON>Margaret Thatcher</PERSON> #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @GoteamAlice: <URL>http://tweetphoto.com/21038079</URL> <PARTY>labour</PARTY> committee room kitty #<PARTY>labour</PARTY>doorstep #<LOCATION>islings</LOCATION> #<LOCATION>islington</LOCATION> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S><PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY>=Smaller class sizes. <PARTY>Labour</PARTY>/<PARTY>Tories</PARTY> want power for powers sake. #ukelection #ge2010 #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> #IAgreeWith<PERSON>Nick</PERSON></S> 
<S>RT @Ajouk Liberal Democracy, personal liberty within a caring, responsible society. Vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY> on Thursday! #ge2010</S> 
<S>Please vote tomorrow to keep the <ORGANIZATION>NHS</ORGANIZATION> in safe hands. #WeLoveThe<ORGANIZATION>NHS</ORGANIZATION> #Vote<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> #UKElection #GE2010</S> 
<S>Where the parties stand: <URL>http://is.gd/bVCzO</URL> #ge2010 #NO2ID</S> 
<S>RT @multimedian: Poll card not arrived? You do NOT need one to vote, go to polling station and give name/address.  PlsRT #GE2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>IMPORTANT comparison Passion 04/05toNOW @socialmention <URL>http://bit.ly/ae7q7l</URL> etc.30hrs NC(39)41;GB(21)23;DC(32)33 #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>40% for <PARTY>LibDems</PARTY> tomorrow = <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> PM. Its in our grasp, just believe #ge2010 #ukelection #vote<PARTY>libdem</PARTY></S> 
<S>RT @ToscaSofia: Super Indy article showing why a <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> govt. would be a DISASTER! <URL>www.independent.co.uk</URL>Ã‚Â» #ge2010 #fuck<PERSON>davidcameron</PERSON> #iagre </S> 
<S>RT @Ajouk Vote for fair taxation, vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY>! #ge2010</S> 
<S>Vote <PERSON>Tory Oilslick</PERSON> if you love the Private Health Service #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @Jameslewisland: #imnotvotingconservative because I like foxes and the gays. #ge2010 #leadersdebate</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: " A complete rehaul of funding for further and higher..." <URL>http://is.gd/bP8BC</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Super Indy article showing why a <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> govt. would be a DISASTER! <URL>http://bit.ly/dzxwiv</URL> #ge2010 #fuck<PERSON>davidcameron</PERSON></S> 
<S>A very well decorated house in <LOCATION>Brigg</LOCATION>! #ge2010  <URL>http://tweetphoto.com/21180107</URL></S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @HouseofTwits: RT @eljmayes TNS-BRMB Poll- <PARTY>CON</PARTY> 33 <PARTY>LIB DEM</PARTY> 29 <PARTY>LAB</PARTY> 27 #GE2010</S> 
<S>tmg social election poll tool is complete, now for a bold seat by seat prediction and analysis: <URL>http://bit.ly/9Ny8nB</URL> #ge2010 #election #tmg</S> 
<S>Most likely #ge2010 scenario? <PARTY>CON</PARTY> win tomorrow, years of austerity allow LD build on the last few wks and mount real challenge next election</S> 
<S><URL>http://bit.ly/bj9bRX</URL> foul mouthed racist homophobes aka Xbox Live players want <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY> win... #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @VoteNoToBNP: <ORGANIZATION>BBC London News</ORGANIZATION> at 1830 has footage of #<PARTY>BNP</PARTY> and youths fighting in <LOCATION>Barking</LOCATION>.  #ge2010 (via @mattcooke_uk)</S> 
<S>#<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> followers clearly have a problem with <PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY> dominating <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> front page tomorrow - Jealousy is such a nasty thing! #GE2010</S> 
<S>More than a little anxious. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Immigration mess was out of control in 2006 &amp; the points system does not allow excluding <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> citizens!!! #vote4change #<PARTY>CONSERVATIVE</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>@BBCRoryCJ well it will if you give it free publicity!!!!!  #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>#10WW #GE2010 the end is nigh!! (in a good way) Do you think <PERSON>Gordon</PERSON> has started packing yet? <URL>http://www.tenwordwiki.com/tactical_voting</URL></S> 
<S><PERSON>John-Paul Rye</PERSON> is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Windsor</LOCATION> Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/bor72r</URL> &amp; <URL>http://windsor.ukindependenceparty.co.uk</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @paulfcockburn hopes, tomorrow, people remember ABC -- Anything But <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>.Well, except the <PARTY>BNP</PARTY>, obviously #ge2010 #<PARTY>Tory</PARTY>Win #Vote<PARTY>Tory</PARTY>...</S> 
<S>Not looking forward to voting tomorrow. Infact bloody worried about it... #ge2010 especially if #<PERSON>clegg</PERSON> the shmuck gets in</S> 
<S>give em hell #bbcqt #ukelection #ge2010 #ge10 #thisweek #<LOCATION>lutons</LOCATION> #ukpolitics #<LOCATION>lutons</LOCATION> #bigotedwoman #uknews #ta2010</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: " The British people should vote for whoever they want..." <URL>http://is.gd/bR2AQ</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @theneweconomics: Pre-election reading - Transforming welfare: new economies, New <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> and the new <PARTY>Tories</PARTY>. <URL>http://bit.ly/bVeWyy</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>Q: So will the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> plastering themselves over the front page of <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> tomorrow in a bid to get more votes backfire or not? #ge2010</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: " Stop <ORGANIZATION>NHS</ORGANIZATION> funding  for therapies like homeopathy that..." <URL>http://is.gd/bP9QK</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>The <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> rally in #<LOCATION>Bristol</LOCATION> will be live streamed on the <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> website <URL>http://ow.ly/1HlP5</URL> #ge2010 #<PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY></S> 
<S>RT @GdnPolitics: How to hold a great election night party, by <PERSON>Zoe Williams</PERSON> <URL>http://bit.ly/diWbvt</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>yayay <PERSON>nick cleggy</PERSON>!!!!!!! :3 :3 :3 #go<PERSON>nick</PERSON> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: " Invest heavily in renewable energy. Without energy..." <URL>http://is.gd/bPZaz</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Poor show, YT: RT @C4election <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> homepage will be taken over by the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> tomorrow, main advert sold to them for the whole day #ge2010</S> 
<S>Only another 28 hours until the Respect noise pollution bus goes away and shuts up for another five years.  I can hardly wait #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @Kat_Cann: #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> 4 #ukelection #ge2010 #imvoting<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> and I #disobey<PERSON>murdoch</PERSON> because #iagreewith<PERSON>nick</PERSON> &amp; def.not #ph ...</S> 
<S>RT @Vote_UKIP <PERSON>Robin Johnson</PERSON> is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Rochester</LOCATION> and #<LOCATION>Strood</LOCATION> Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/9DSIvv</URL> #GE2010 <URL>http://bit.ly/cTIYBO</URL></S> 
<S><PERSON>Pearline Hingston</PERSON> is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Southampton</LOCATION> Test Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/cJKnjw</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>Wd like to see <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> rightofreply but this is important #ge2010 read on <LOCATION>Hammersmith</LOCATION>. <URL>http://bit.ly/afXzGQ</URL></S> 
<S>Not seen this before - <ORGANIZATION>Google</ORGANIZATION> enters the electoral fray! <URL>http://bit.ly/97gAJc</URL>  #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @multimedian: Poll card not arrived? You do NOT need one to vote, go to polling station and give name/address Pls RT #GE2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Hilarious attack on <PARTY>tories</PARTY>! VIDEO #iagreewith<PERSON>nick</PERSON> #ge2010 <URL>http://is.gd/bVwTS</URL></S> 
<S>How any #<PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY> can use the word bigot in their tweet attacking someone else is beyond me. #ge2010</S> 
<S><URL>http://twitpic.com/1lam9d</URL> <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> arriving at <LOCATION>Eddie Stobart HQ</LOCATION> #ge2010</S> 
<S>@krishgm this letter in my local paper about the incumbent <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> MP <PERSON>David Amess</PERSON> made me laugh <URL>http://twitpic.com/1laln8</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>John Meropoulos</PERSON> (@UKIPRomSoton) is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Romsey</LOCATION> and #<LOCATION>Southampton North</LOCATION> Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/aR5BNS</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>Some assessments of the #ukelection campaign as the end approaches <URL>http://bit.ly/dyb54a</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @GaeMar01: RT @TheSamCamFoetus: Why is <PERSON>David #Cameron</PERSON> cancelling so many interviews, is he running scared from himself? #Ge2010 #Ge10 #Ge</S> 
<S>Current results: 2nd <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> Party with 10.74% See <URL>www.twitVoteUK.org.uk</URL> for more info  #twitVoteUK #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>#imnotvotingconservative because I like foxes and the gays.  #ge2010 #leadersdebate</S> 
<S>RT @angelneptustar: Who besides me wants <PERSON>Ed Balls</PERSON> to get a massive kick in the ballot box 2moro?  #election2010  #bigotgate  #ge2010  #ge10</S> 
<S>RT @WalaaIdris <ORGANIZATION>Daily Express</ORGANIZATION> poll <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> 35 - <PARTY>Lab</PARTY> 27  - <PARTY>LiD</PARTY> 26 #GE2010</S> 
<S>Is it just me or has <PERSON>griffin</PERSON> got absolutely no chance of winning the <LOCATION>barking</LOCATION> seat? #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @SNPofficial: <PERSON>Alex Salmond</PERSON> campaigning in <LOCATION>Denny</LOCATION> for <PERSON>John McNally</PERSON> #<PARTY>snp</PARTY> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>does anyone know of a website that will tell you the candidates in your area? #GE2010</S> 
<S>If <URL>http://bit.ly/aGzZpc</URL> is to believed then 28 <PARTY>labour</PARTY> and 92 <PARTY>libdem</PARTY> PPCs signed a pledge against abortion and lgbt rights. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Opininum/<ORGANIZATION>Daily Express</ORGANIZATION> Poll- <PARTY>CON</PARTY> 35 <PARTY>LAB</PARTY> 27 <PARTY>LIB DEM</PARTY> 26 #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @theelectionblog: RT @TelegraphNews <PERSON>Robert Mugabe</PERSON> gives <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> election backing - <ORGANIZATION>Telegraph</ORGANIZATION> <URL>http://bit.ly/9o0CMJ</URL> #GE2010 #UKEL ...</S> 
<S>RT @tanngrisnir: RT @elmyra: The further I get into this article, the sicker I feel: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/2vkhwaw</URL> #ge2010 &lt;- Yes; every ...</S>
<S>RT @mark_simpson: <PERSON>Robert Mugabe</PERSON> backs <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> to win.  <URL>http://digg.com/d11KfvX</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @LSEelectionblog: Eve of the election: reflections from <ORGANIZATION>LSE</ORGANIZATION> Election Experts <URL>http://blogs.lse.ac.uk/election/?p=2052</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @TanktheTories: #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY> BECAUSE <PERSON>ROBERT MUGABE</PERSON> BACKS THE <PARTY>CONSERVATIVES</PARTY> - <ORGANIZATION>Telegraph</ORGANIZATION> <URL>http://bit.ly/9o0CMJ</URL> #GE2010 #ukelection</S>
<S>I agree with <PERSON>Franny</PERSON> <URL>http://bit.ly/bLATQL</URL> #firstGreenMPs #ge2010</S> 
<S><URL>http://twitter.com/innerhippy/statuses/13434542158</URL> Right on tech, but <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> is best for economy. Do not blame Captain for the storm #ge2010</S> 
<S>On the eve of the election - An Open letter to party leaders: <URL>http://bit.ly/94flWI</URL></S> 
<S>RT @angelneptustar: <URL>http://bit.ly/cXbSFF</URL> <LOCATION>Durham</LOCATION> students yell at <PERSON>Clegg</PERSON> What price the new politics?  #bigotgate  #election2010  #ge2010  ...</S> 
<S>RT @CardomeCards: RT @ajpatty:  <PERSON>David Stroud</PERSON> signs Xian extremist declaration <URL>http://bit.ly/cccgEl</URL> #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud</PERSON> #ge2010 #election2010</S> 
<S>Think about this before you vote <PARTY>Tory</PARTY>. <URL>http://bit.ly/bpAkDC</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @twitNIelection: UKelection2010: <ORGANIZATION>Wall Street Journal</ORGANIZATION> - Uphill Battle for Small <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> Parties in #ge2010 <URL>http://is.gd/bVicw</URL>: <URL>http://url4</URL>. </S>
<S>RT @IndepNet: A message from "Sleaze Buster" <PERSON>Martin Bell</PERSON> <URL>http://bit.ly/bF913c</URL>#ge2010 #hangem #ukelection #imnotvoting</S> 
<S>Is <LOCATION>Bartholomew Street</LOCATION> the most political street in SE1?  <URL>http://twitpic.com/1lacbm</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>Is it true <PARTY>conservatives</PARTY> have bought <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> for the whole of tomorrow? #GE2010</S> 
<S>Cashcroft <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> chucking money at <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> tomorrow - panic or desperation? #GE2010</S>
<S>RT @multimedian: Poll card not arrived? You do NOT need one to vote, go to polling station and give name/address Pls RT #GE2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @irevdrdab: A great new song to sing about #<PERSON>phillipastroud</PERSON> by my good friend @Steeluloid ~ <URL>http://tinyurl.com/375twlf</URL> #ge2010 #homophobia</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: " Repeal the Digital Economy Bill" <URL>http://is.gd/bR1ms</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @OpenRightsGroup: 750 demand repeal of #DEAct today: sign the petition! <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #debill #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @electionpredict Interesting chart: Without TV debates <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> would have one foot in Downing Street <URL>http://bit.ly/behE9U</URL> #GE2010 #GE10</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: "Invest seriously in properly thought through provision..." <URL>http://is.gd/bR1jr</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.07 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI</S> 
<S>RT @C4election: <ORGANIZATION>YouTube</ORGANIZATION> homepage will be taken over by the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> tomorrow main advert has been sold to the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> for the whole day #ge2010</S> 
<S>@WilliamJHague Good luck tomorrow personally &amp; party. <PERSON>DC</PERSON> for PM. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @RateMyTory: RT @Progressonline: 100 achievements of this <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> government, 100 reasons why #ImVoting<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> - #ge10 #ge2010 #ukelect ...</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act (<LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> only) <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>To see if the <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> idea will work can anyone tell me the current advert on <ORGANIZATION>YouTubes</ORGANIZATION> home? #ge2010</S> 
<S>Saw <PERSON>john stanely</PERSON> (mp tonbridge and malling <PARTY>conservative</PARTY>) down town, walked on by to avoid flaming about #debill / #deact #ge2010</S> 
<S>@parsingphase As I explained, still getting caught up.  :) #ge2010</S> 
<S>Teen research: 16-17 year olds most likely to vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY> <URL>http://bit.ly/cHvKAn</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Election 2010: LEWIS PR social media survey in the New Statesman <URL>http://tinyurl.com/2cy43py</URL> #ge2010 #lewispr</S> 
<S>RT @BBCLauraK <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> have bought space on the front page of <ORGANIZATION>Youtube</ORGANIZATION> for all of polling day #GE2010 #Ge10  #ToryWin #VoteTory #philippastroud</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @timespolitics: BLOG: Still undecided about who to vote for? The web can help <URL>http://bit.ly/cjBmuX</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @leesmallwood: General Election: How many people feel like her? #ge2010 <URL>http://ping.fm/dUDJk</URL></S> 
<S>RT @TheCornishDem: I am voting for #mebyonkernow because I believe <LOCATION>Cornwall</LOCATION> should have a greater say over its own governance. #ge2010</S> 
<S>If you are sick of old politics then watch this <URL>http://bit.ly/aMxMj9</URL> and then help us change it #youreit #tothecommons #ge2010 #tamsinomond</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>The <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> bubble well and truly burst... Poor ickle <PERSON>Nicky</PERSON> now being mocked by students on <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> over expenses. #GE2010</S> 
<S>BBC News strapline: "<PERSON>Clegg</PERSON>: I will do everything to make things better." *Everything*? He can start with my washing up, then. #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Clegg</PERSON>: "This time you can make a difference". #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @cllrtheo #ge2010 Picture of <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> with gay-curer #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud</PERSON> <URL>http://tinyurl.com/38g7g7n</URL> Caption contest?</S> 
<S>RT @Kat_Cann: #imnotvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> 4 #ukelection #ge2010 #imvotinglibdem and I #disobeymurdoch because #iagreewith<PERSON>nick</PERSON> &amp; def.not #ph ...</S> 
<S>RT @StopTheRight #<PERSON>PhillippaStroud</PERSON> - regards stopping abortion as a key issue. <URL>http://alturl.com/gwge</URL>  #ge2010 #ukelection #24weeks</S> 
<S>The leading party in our poll has changed in <LOCATION>HUNTINGDON</LOCATION>, and is now the <PARTY>Liberal Democrat Party</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @MuslimCouncil: #<PERSON>nickclegg</PERSON> of #<PARTY>libdems</PARTY> respond to questions posed by Muslim Vote 2010 #ge2010 <URL>http://ow.ly/1Hebn</URL></S> 
<S>"Why Endorse The <PARTY>Tories</PARTY>? ... ItÃ¢Â€Â™s utterly bizarre." <PERSON>Paul Krugman</PERSON>; <URL>http://tinyurl.com/282r5nd</URL>  #GE2010 @evanhd @johnprescott @campbellclaret</S> 
<S>RT @OpenRightsGroup: 750 demand repeal of #DEAct today: sign the petition! <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #debill #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @jordannewell: Campaign moves to Prettygate #jordan4colchester #labourdoorstep #<LOCATION>Colchester</LOCATION> #GE2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Mazhar Manzoor</PERSON> is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Guildford</LOCATION> Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/dzldbi<URL> &amp; </URL>http://guildford.ukip.org</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>@AledR he probably meant the most "rich-family-friendly country in <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>".  #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>So come and join us for all the main <LOCATION>Bradford</LOCATION> and district election news as it happens #ge2010</S> 
<S>For those of you wanting to keep up with the #GE2010 night in <LOCATION>Scotland</LOCATION>- BBC Parliament will take the Scottish feed tomorrow.</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON> closing campaign rally in <LOCATION>Bristol</LOCATION> 6pm tonight? <URL>http://bit.ly/cgEwjR</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #<LOCATION>bristol</LOCATION></S> 
<S>A polictial party leader that is human does exist! <ORGANIZATION>Guardian</ORGANIZATION> article - <URL>http://gu.com/p/2gn5y/tw</URL> #ge2010 #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> #ukelection</S> 
<S><PERSON>Robert Mugabe</PERSON> would vote #<PARTY>Tory</PARTY> &amp; <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>. <URL>http://bit.ly/abZogo</URL>  Want a Zimbabwean version of Britain? You know what to do tomorrow. #GE2010</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.06 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: " lets give people with learning disabilities real..." <URL>http://is.gd/bOSH5</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>5th phone call for an update from the <ORGANIZATION>London police</ORGANIZATION> - as recent crime victim they have been excellent ! thanks to <PARTY>Labour</PARTY>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>Gods, this is unbelievably smug... <URL>http://bit.ly/bYTgqX</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Trending This Afternoon: "Lower traffic speeds in urban areas where people live,..." <URL>://is.gd/bR0HH</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Not long to go now till #ge2010 D-Day! I will be at <LOCATION>Manc Town Hall</LOCATION> for the <LOCATION>Withington</LOCATION> count - shall be liveblogging and tweeting!</S> 
<S>@Jackiepearcey @YasminQureshi @Deborahdunleavy, take a look at our <LOCATION>Bolton</LOCATION> predictions <URL>http://bit.ly/9XHMPm</URL> for #GE2010 can <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> hold?</S> 
<S>@timeshighered thought you might like this: stats on youth/ twenties vote <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3a5r45q</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #geny</S> 
<S>Ed Balls: Vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY>...ok! I will! #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @harikunzru: <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leafletting black voters in <LOCATION>Dagenham</LOCATION>. Divide and rule <URL>http://bit.ly/dinQkC</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @bumblebums: Freedland: Remember 1983? I warn you that a <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> victory will be just as bad <URL>http://is.gd/bVlV2</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @benjohnbarnes: If you're planning to vote #<PARTY>Tory</PARTY> in #ge2010, please take a read of <URL>http://j.mp/d1SoMH</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @harikunzru: <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> leafletting black voters in Dagenham. Divide and rule <URL>http://bit.ly/dinQkC</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Today been in <LOCATION>Castle</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Berechurch</LOCATION>. <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> activists now heading off to New Town.  #<PARTY>labour</PARTY>doorstep  #GE2010  #Colchester</S> 
<S>RT @elmyra: The further I get into this article, the sicker I feel: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/2vkhwaw</URL> #ge2010 &lt;- Yes; everyone should read it.</S> 
<S><PERSON>Simon Cowell</PERSON> backs <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON>: A megalomaniac who sits on a panel of suck-ups that shout at commoners. But enough about <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>.. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @SkyNews Are you one of the 38% undecided? Let <ORGANIZATION>skynews.com</ORGANIZATION>/whoshouldivotefor help you decide #ge2010 <URL>http://bit.ly/deT9qh</URL></S> 
<S><PARTY>Tories</PARTY> <PERSON>deny Warsi</PERSON> said Muslims in Parliament "don't have any morals or principles". Read more <URL>http://bit.ly/bXDfMI</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Betting odds seem to be moving against <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> majority in a significant way. But there's been no new poll. Weird. #ge2010</S> 
<S>@stack72 It's as good as voting RON (ah the good old days of <ORGANIZATION>STV</ORGANIZATION>) #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @Conservatives: We've wasted Ã‚Â£12 million trying to buy this election. Now trust us with your money. #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @mattlingard: Exec summary of <ORGANIZATION>LSE</ORGANIZATION> research on election issues <URL>http://is.gd/bVhFT</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>I have 0.222! Yay FPP! RT @TomWhitwell Where I live I have the power of 0.12 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S><URL>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=psxx2nnwf10</URL> #knifecrime #qpr please RT THESE are the issues politicians need to sort #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @blue_espresso: Unlike many #<PARTY>labour</PARTY> supporters, even though I don't agree with your views, I do respect your right to have them #ge2010</S> 
<S>@StarSparkle_UK Currently number 3 of 10 in the <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> trend list. #ImNotVotingConservative #UKElection #GE2010</S> 
<S>#votegreen RT @doctoreno: #GE2010 Recent Opinion Poll in <LOCATION>Cambridge</LOCATION> puts the <PARTY>Greens</PARTY> in the lead:</S>
<S>Canine testicles, <PERSON>Jedward</PERSON>, and <ORGANIZATION>Nazis</ORGANIZATION>. The blog that has it all, except anything resembling sanity. <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3845ea4</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.06 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI still going to vote tho &amp; give a view</S> 
<S>One last Ponty candidate to meet: <PERSON>Mike Powell</PERSON> for the <PARTY>Liberal Democrats</PARTY> <URL>http://ow.ly/1HfIb</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @quantick No! Sleep! Til! Prep! &lt;&lt; Ha! Ha! Ha! #ge2010 #ukelection #WorkingTimeDirectiveOutOfTheWindowUnderTheTories</S> 
<S>#<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> #<PARTY>libDem</PARTY> #<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> #<PARTY>green</PARTY> #<PARTY>pirate</PARTY>party - which way will you vote this Thursday? Watch the alternative election @LGoS #fb #ge2010</S> 
<S>Having postal voted I can't help but think that tomorrow might feel a little anticlimactic. Am currently hopeful but not optimistic #ge2010</S> 
<S>There is a sweepstake in my office for the #ge2010 results for seat numbers - do you have predictions @directhex?</S> 
<S>My 'how to vote' quiz results at <URL>http://whoshouldyouvotefor.com</URL>: <PARTY>LIB</PARTY>+20 <PARTY>LAB</PARTY>+16 <PARTY>GRN</PARTY>+8 <URL>http://wsyvf.com/uk/6lNOISAm2EN6oLgf</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Gordon Brown's</PERSON> speech at Citizens <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION>is rising increadibly. 95,000 views now and counting! Watch it here: <URL>http://alturl.com/qtxb</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>@Joanne_Cash good luck tomorrow <PERSON>Joanne</PERSON>. You have been one of the true twitter #ge2010 stars. C u next week <URL>http://pdfge2010.eventbrite.com/</URL></S> 
<S>More evidence <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> wants to drink like common people, common people like you #GE2010 <URL>http://twitpic.com/1l9f50</URL></S> 
<S><PERSON>Howard Farmer</PERSON> is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Canterbury</LOCATION> Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/cXo7ab</URL> &amp; <URL>http://ukipcanterbury.blogspot.com</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @slewth: A short post on accessible ditigal election resources <URL>http://bit.ly/a5Et4C</URL> #ge2010 #a11y #digitalinclusion</S> 
<S>Where possible tomorrow, vote for a socialist. Where possible vote #<PARTY>ssp</PARTY> Where needed,keep the <PARTY>tories</PARTY> out. #ge10 #ge2010 #UKelection</S> 
<S>Hear hear! RT @adders: Ladies &amp; gents I honestly don't care whom you vote for, as long as  _you do vote_.  That's what democracy is. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @thejimsmith: #imvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> just as soon as I have this inconvenient empathy amputated. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Exec summary of <ORGANIZATION>LSE</ORGANIZATION> research on election issues <URL>http://is.gd/bVhFT</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @jonronson: A beautiful, horrific piece of writing from @johannhari101 <URL>http://bit.ly/9ktLTH</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Who's on First? RT @yourPonty Meet another candidate: <PERSON>Simon Parsons</PERSON> for <PARTY>Socialist Labour</PARTY> <URL>http://ow.ly/1HeW8</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Election tomorrow! Question: vote for invisible, insubstantial <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> candidate, or vote <PARTY>Lib Dem</PARTY> tactically to keep <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> out? #ge2010</S> 
<S>#HarrietHarman ANSWER THE QUESTION!! oh dear!! #GE2010</S> 
<S>@repost Blogged: This Blog Endorses.... <URL>http://bit.ly/aMbSEQ</URL> #ge2010 #ge10 #ukelection</S> 
<S>Johann Hari: Welcome to <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> land <URL>http://bit.ly/dickRa</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @alanmills405: ""Remember 1983? I warn you a <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> victory will be just as bad" <ORGANIZATION>Guardian</ORGANIZATION> <URL>http://tinyurl.com/23j2nr4</URL>  #ge2010 #ge10"</S> 
<S>In the spirit of fairness, Gnews will vote for all parties tomorrow (apart from the ones we don't like) #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @comosa: RT @johannhari101 Welcome to <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON>-Land <URL>http://bit.ly/9ktLTH</URL> - Amazing article, should be read by everyone. #ge2010</S> 
<S>The <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> are now very likely to punch below their weight in <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION> debates,leaving others to shape the future direction of the <ORGANIZATION>EU</ORGANIZATION>. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Whoever you vote for tomorrow - The Government will always win #ge2010</S> 
<S>@FT stats on youth/ twenties vote <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3a5r45q #ukelection</URL> #ge2010 #geny</S> 
<S>@tweetminster stats on youth/ twenties vote <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3a5r45q</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #geny</S> 
<S>@forrester thought you might like this <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3a5r45q</URL> #ukelection #ge2010 #geny</S> 
<S>RT @carlmaxim: If you are suffering from #imvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> then <PERSON>Philippa Stroud</PERSON> can cure you #phillippastroud #philippastroud #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @ElectionLength: <PARTY>BNP's</PARTY> website manager resigns and takes their website down a day before the General Election: <URL>http://bit.ly/akL1C0</URL>   Hahaha! #GE2010</S> 
<S>What could happen: Hung Parliament  <URL>http://bit.ly/b3FlrH</URL> #GE2010 #GE10 #UKElection #UK2010</S> 
<S>Dr <PERSON>David Sebastian Fairweather</PERSON> is standing for #<PARTY>UKIP</PARTY> in #<LOCATION>Banbury</LOCATION> Ã¢Â€Â? <URL>http://bit.ly/cqrx55</URL> &amp; <URL>http://bit.ly/9cpnE3</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>25 years ago <PERSON>John Cleese</PERSON> explained PR  voting,  coalition governments and the evils of a 2 party system <URL>http://tinyurl.com/3y8o2jn</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S><PARTY>BNP</PARTY> in turmoil after online chief <PERSON>Simon Bennett</PERSON> walks out - <ORGANIZATION>Times</ORGANIZATION> Online: <URL>http://bit.ly/cT926C</URL> via @addthis #ukelection #ge2010 #ge10</S> 
<S><PERSON>Brian Taylor's</PERSON> blog: All part of the service <URL>http://bit.ly/9egt2c</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>#Politics: derived from 2 words; poly - means many, &amp; tics - means small blood-sucking insects!</S>
<S>RT @Blue_Espresso: #imvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> because I don't want to be disadvantaged just because I provide for my family #voteforchange #<PARTY>Conservative</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>#imvoting<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> because #<PARTY>labour</PARTY> hasn't made it illegal to do, so I can still use my common sense #voteforchange #<PARTY>Conservative</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @GaeMar01: RT @rugbyrose: <PERSON>Simon Cowell</PERSON>, multimillionaire who doesn't live here, exploits desperate and mentally ill for a living,  backs <PARTY>Conser</PARTY> #Ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @alexjbutcher: Excellent <PERSON>Charlie Stross</PERSON> blog on #ge2010 - <URL>http://bit.ly/9tbpn9</URL> . Remarkably similar to my own views, in all respects.</S> 
<S>RT @Quinns108 Retweet, people. This <PERSON>Phillipa Stroud</PERSON> story seems to have come to lawsuit-related standstill. <URL>http://bit.ly/98usim</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @Quinns108: Retweet, people. This <PERSON>Phillipa Stroud</PERSON> story seems to have come to lawsuit-related standstill. <URL>http://bit.ly/98usim</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @graemelambert Another database lost in <PARTY>Labour's</PARTY> <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION>! - <URL>http://bit.ly/cNfuPx</URL> #vote<PARTY>pirate</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>#imvotingconservative because, like <PERSON>Simon Cowell</PERSON> and <PERSON>Gary Barlow</PERSON>, I am a cunt. /via @DanielNothing #GOLD #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @manwiddicombe: RT <PERSON>@ArmyofDave</PERSON> Today's Blog: A Guide To Voting Etiquette: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/2bx3k39</URL> #ge2010 #ge10 &lt;-- essential reading</S> 
<S><ORGANIZATION>Sky News</ORGANIZATION> interviewing <PERSON>Ed Balls</PERSON>, for whom lying is much easier than breathing. #ge2010</S> 
<S>@GetLabourOut you do know that @UKlabourparty is a fake account? The offical <PARTY>labour</PARTY> account is @uklabour #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @jemimakiss: RT @nachimir: <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> candidate #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud's</PERSON> lawyers have gagged her victims and the press: <URL>http://TwitPWR.com/IzK/</URL> #ge2010 #<PARTY>conservatives</PARTY></S> 
<S>@NigelThorley That is a fair comment, and the outcome of #ge2010 could also make a big difference</S> 
<S>RT @PR1ZEFIGHTER Remember to vote tomorrow guys! #ge2010 Good luck to all the @PiratePartyUK  Candidates, and good luck @tom_watson #DEBill</S> 
<S>RT @johnprescott: Wonder if #idontagreewithcowell will start trending #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY> #ge10 #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @higgis: <PERSON>George Osborne</PERSON>. Making decisions that affect your life. Think about it. Then vote to make it impossible. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Hope we're all going to vote tomorrow (in the <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION>, that is). I hate it when people moan about the Govt, then say they <ORGANIZATION>CBA</ORGANIZATION> voting. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Today's Blog: A Guide To Voting Etiquette: <URL>http://tinyurl.com/2bx3k39</URL> #ge2010 #ge10</S> 
<S>RT @twitVoteUK: The <PARTY>Liberal Democrat Party</PARTY> are leading the poll; with 336 out of 472 constituencies  <URL>twitvoteuk.org.uk</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>The <PARTY>Liberal Democrat Party</PARTY> are leading the poll; with 336 out of 472 constituencies  <URL>twitvoteuk.org.uk</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @c4election: Astute kids <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> was talking to this morning. One deduced where <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> and co had been earlier saying "you all smell of fish". #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @TheRVT: Scottee is Building Expectations: @reply us what you expect from any new government and be part of his installation tonight #ge2010</S> 
<S>@nick_reeve But you can change hat power. Every vote always counts to changing the political landscape. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @malkinbister: <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> online chief quits, takes site down with him. Now *that's* how to sod off in style <URL>http://bit.ly/bx4itb</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @newsnetscotland: <PARTY>SNP</PARTY> boost as final <ORGANIZATION>YouGov</ORGANIZATION> poll shows late surge <URL>http://bit.ly/9zlXfO</URL> - #ge2010 #scotland #scotlandspeaks #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @TeleElection: <PERSON>Nick Clegg</PERSON> asks voters to 'lend' their support <URL>http://tgr.ph/9d6LzK</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>A harrowing article in light of tomorrow: <URL>http://bit.ly/9ktLTH</URL>  I wish someone would pay for this, for shame: <URL>http://bit.ly/aw45TE</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>How 'Big Society' currently works in <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> councils.</S> 
<S>RT @C4election: So <ORGANIZATION>Twitter</ORGANIZATION>, how much of what you write will come true tomorrow? <URL>http://ow.ly/1HdeN</URL>  #ge2010 #ge10</S> 
<S>building luxury flats but theres a pesky homeless shelter in the way?call #<PERSON>cameron</PERSON> .read <URL>http://bit.ly/apDStR</URL> #toryfail #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>@IWILLNOTGOAWAY Don't forget #<LOCATION>Iraq</LOCATION>, #Chilcot, #Expenses, #IDcards, #42days, #DEBill, #10pTax when you vote tomorrow #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @dandelion101: @UKLabour #ImVoting<PARTY>Labour</PARTY> because I hate poor people, I hate civil liberties, I hate truth and justice and I hate the British people #ge2010</S> 
<S>@concretefox <PERSON>Michael Gove</PERSON> - looks like a slapped child and sounds like <PERSON>Graham Norton</PERSON> complaining about a crap sandwich #ge2010</S> 
<S>@<PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY> Always good to get the support of foreign billionaires! #GE2010</S> 
<S>Just wrong. <URL>http://bit.ly/bpAkDC</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>I emailed local candidates re 38degrees end-secret-lobbying campaign, and <PERSON>Helen Flynn</PERSON> (<PARTY>LD</PARTY>) replied from her phone within minutes. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @LSEelectionblog: New <PERSON>Hix-Vivyan</PERSON> prediction: <PARTY>Con</PARTY>/<PARTY>Lab</PARTY> seat gap could be as little as 18!  <URL>http://is.gd/bVcfb</URL> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @timespolitics: <PARTY>BNP</PARTY> in turmoil after online chief <PERSON>Simon Bennett</PERSON> walks out <URL>http://bit.ly/bx4itb</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @electionpredict: <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> scraps for seats as election hangs in balance <URL>http://bit.ly/afyBtw</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.77 votes, 3 times the national average. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI</S> 
<S>@RobCutforth // srsly one of the best breakdowns i've seen #ge2010 - if it weren't for all the blow &amp; that dead hooker, you could make a run</S> 
<S>Ã¢Â™Â» @ppinternational #votepirate Everybody now: please RETWEET this to help @PiratePartyUK in the #ukelection #ge2010 Cross your fingers !!!</S> 
<S>RT @libdemsnews: Brilliant #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> video from the <LOCATION>london</LOCATION> flashmob of a couple of  days back <URL>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tO46i6OF90Q</URL> #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @Quinns108: Retweet, people. This <PERSON>Phillipa Stroud</PERSON> story seems to have come to lawsuit-related standstill. <URL>http://bit.ly/98usim</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S><PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY>: Party of the rich, by the rich, for the rich. Great article by <PERSON>Johann Hari</PERSON> <URL>http://bit.ly/dzxwiv</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Just a quick reminder that a vote for <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> = a vote for complicity in TORTURE  - look to your conscience before you vote #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @majestic_whine: This article is an eye opener. The reality behind <PERSON>Camerons</PERSON> 'big society' <URL>http://tinyurl.com/2vkhwaw</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @and_14_all: #toptips <PERSON>David Cameron</PERSON>. Fed up with rolling up those sleeves? Buy yourself a T shirt you insomniacTory twat  #ge2010</S> 
<S>How many candidates are relying on artificial stimulants to get through the final few days? #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @Democraticist: @andy_s_64  FREE DIGITAL HEARING AIDS + FREE BATTERIES ... Thanks to <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> #GE2010</S> 
<S>I agreed most with <PERSON>Hugh Bayley</PERSON> (<PARTY>Labour Party</PARTY>) in <LOCATION>York Central</LOCATION> - how about you? <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL> @democlub #ge2010 #YorkC</S> 
<S>@jo_beckett i spelt it correct on the letter .. what a waste of money for the <PARTY>CONServatives</PARTY> to send to a loyal Labourite #vote<PARTY>labour</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>VOTE for #<PERSON>BROWN</PERSON> and get SUE but choose #<PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> and get SCREWED #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>ONE STOP/CLICK SHOP for all twitterers/bookies odds >300 marginal constituencies + info <URL>http://bit.ly/9iBmjM</URL> &amp; @eMay06MP/frontline  #GE2010</S> 
<S>I agreed most with <PERSON>Barry Stamp</PERSON> (<PARTY>Liberal Democrats</PARTY>) in <LOCATION>Stafford</LOCATION> - how about you? <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL> @democlub #ge2010 #Stafford</S> 
<S>The <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> hasn't had any big riots since the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> were last in power. Remember that tomorrow when you vote. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.1 votes. See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI</S> 
<S>Worth a read <URL>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/a1962318.html</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @BridgetFox: <ORGANIZATION>Independent</ORGANIZATION> joins <ORGANIZATION>Guardian</ORGANIZATION> in urging folk to vote <PARTY>LibDem</PARTY> in <LOCATION>Islington</LOCATION> #ge2010 #<LOCATION>IslingS</LOCATION></S> 
<S>RT @shiningwitevent: <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> too tired to do R 5 interview? Just the sort of stamina we want from a PM... Meeting with G20? Sorry <PERSON>Gideon</PERSON>, I need a nap #ge2010</S> 
<S>@billybragg A hung parliament doesn't always result in consensus - more often it results in incoherent horse-trading. #GE2010</S> 
<S>Anyone in <LOCATION>Camden High Street</LOCATION>? <PERSON>Vince Cable</PERSON> will be there shortly #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Dave's</PERSON> last throw of the homophobic dice: <URL>http://twitpic.com/1kenfa</URL> #GE2010 #UKElection</S> 
<S>Under Previous <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> governments we have never won the World Cup but we did win <ORGANIZATION>Eurovision</ORGANIZATION>. Worth the risk again? #ge2010 #dontvote<PARTY>tory</PARTY></S> 
<S>RT @chickyog: That 'nice' <PERSON>Iain Dale</PERSON> - <URL>http://bit.ly/dagsyM</URL> - If only he'd got a seat, the fun we'd have had... #ge2010</S> 
<S>Racist? Homophobic? Hate Foreigners? Xenophobic? Pro-hunting? want tax cuts for the rich? Religious Nut? Then join the <PARTY>Tory Party</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @ppinternational: #vote<PARTY>pirate</PARTY> Everybody now: please RETWEET this to help @PiratePartyUK in the #ukelection #ge2010 Cross your fingers !!!</S> 
<S>election analysis by <ORGANIZATION>LSE</ORGANIZATION> economists: <URL>http://cep.lse.ac.uk/pubs/download/CEP_ElectionAnalysis_2010.pdf</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>What I'd like from our next government, and why I'm voting for the <PARTY>@LibDems</PARTY>: <URL>http://post.ly/euIz</URL> #UKElection #GE2010 #<LOCATION>Warwick</LOCATION></S> 
<S>#<PERSON>GordonBrown</PERSON> A TRAITOR IN ACTION!! <URL>http://bit.ly/9jLz7F</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @Quinns108: Retweet, people. This <PERSON>Phillipa</PERSON> Stroud story seems to have come to lawsuit-related standstill. <URL>http://bit.ly/98usim</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @benleto: The <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> MPs who voted to keep Clause 28. See who you're voting for before you do <URL>http://bit.ly/bOjC6U</URL> #ge2010 #DontVote<PARTY>Tory</PARTY> #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @graemelambert: Would laugh if everyone backs a hung parliament at the bookies and votes <PARTY>lib dems</PARTY>, and then the <PARTY>lib dems</PARTY> get a shock majority. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @dominiccampbell: RT @zzgavin:'This used 2b a gr8 place to live if you were disabled.Then the <PARTY>tory</PARTY> council was elected' #bigsociety #ge2010 http://j.mp/cFObrZ</S> 
<S>RT @synthjock: <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> must be hallucinating by now from lack of sleep. If a man in a white coat asks him who the prime minister is, he's fucked  #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @mikebutcher: Should <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> based startups vote <PARTY>LibDem</PARTY>? Probably not. <URL>http://bit.ly/9Nlfid</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>CGT on Exit IS income and should be taxed as such. Fight asset strippers and encourage REAL Lasting Industry <URL>http://bit.ly/9c4XIa</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @the_rock_of_gib: VIDEO: <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> Says Its Substance Over Style #<PERSON>gordonbrown</PERSON> #<PARTY>labour</PARTY> #<PARTY>tory</PARTY> #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> #<PARTY>snp</PARTY> #vote2010 #ge2010 #ge10 #... htt ...</S> 
<S>RT @rachelcreative: Just uploaded <PARTY>LibDem</PARTY> leaflet <LOCATION>Lichfield</LOCATION> @TheSC from @democlub http://bit.ly/9rMEEr #ge2010 #<LOCATION>Lichfield</LOCATION> @<LOCATION>Lichfield</LOCATION>GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @TonyJuniper: Check out this website <URL>http://bit.ly/aDBKuD</URL> it's specific to the #<LOCATION>Cambridge</LOCATION> constituency #ge2010</S> 
<S>What the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> may bring..... #ge2010 <URL>http://ht.ly/1Hc0A</URL></S> 
<S>@manatrue My slogan would be Not <PARTY>Tory</PARTY>, Not <PARTY>Labour</PARTY>, #Vote4AnyoneElse (not <PARTY>BNP</PARTY>, obv) #ge2010 #maggieout</S> 
<S>RT @fnohe: RT @giveyourvote: Results from the WORLD'S FIRST CROSS-BORDER ELECTION: <PARTY>Lib Dems</PARTY> 51%, <PARTY>Lab</PARTY> 26%, <PARTY>Con</PARTY> 21% <URL>http://ow.ly/1Haln</URL>  #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @smilerish: After reading this, I've died a little inside: <URL>http://bit.ly/b3eKrV</URL> Please read if you're thinking of voting <PARTY>Tory</PARTY> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @drogersuk: Is this the kind of behaviour you expect from your MP? @adamafriyie #<LOCATION>windsor</LOCATION> #<PARTY>conservative</PARTY> #fail #ukelection #ge2010 http ...</S> 
<S>We love <LOCATION>Leeds</LOCATION> Catering Service - well wishes with our lunch :) <URL>http://twitpic.com/1l8j08</URL> #ge2010 #<PARTY>Labour</PARTY></S> 
<S>RT @aseculargay: <PERSON>David Stroud</PERSON> signs Xian extremist declaration <URL>http://www.ekklesia.co.uk/node/12061</URL> #<PERSON>PhilippaStroud</PERSON> #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S><PARTY>iberal Democrats</PARTY> + <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> hand up combined with <PARTY>Conservative</PARTY> hands off the ideal set of policies #TellYouGov #ge2010</S> 
<S>As ever, a very good article from @johannhari101 - <URL>http://bit.ly/bpAkDC</URL> #GE2010</S> 
<S><URL>http://twitter.com/ardalby/statuses/13421517261</URL> Here after <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> unemployment? Exports rising fastest since 1994, policy working #ge2010</S> 
<S>on <ORGANIZATION>Sky News</ORGANIZATION> tomorrow night with <PERSON>Michael Winner</PERSON> and Tony the Tiger to talk about how #ge2010 will affect miscellaneous shit</S> 
<S><URL>http://twitter.com/drjohnhayward/statuses/13421521742</URL> Taking on mortgage made me rich. Exports rising fastest since 1994 #ge2010 Its working</S> 
<S>RT @Quinns108: Retweet, people. This <PERSON>Phillipa Stroud</PERSON> story seems to have come to lawsuit-related standstill. <URL>http://bit.ly/98usim</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Which oarty leader isgetting the most coverage on Twitter <URL>http://bit.ly/ceb3DN</URL> #bbcqt #ge2010</S> 
<S>Please keep <PERSON>Evan Harris</PERSON> (<LOCATION>Oxford West &amp; Abingdon</LOCATION>) in Parliament - <URL>http://bit.ly/bV8Yyw</URL> - <URL>http://bit.ly/aU8KWg</URL>  #scivote #ukelection #ge2010</S> 
<S>Wi-Fi Lessons to be Learnt | <LOCATION>Swindon</LOCATION> <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> <URL>http://ht.ly/1HbBu</URL> #<LOCATION>swindon</LOCATION><PARTY>tory</PARTY> #<PARTY>conservative</PARTY>council #<LOCATION>swindon</LOCATION> #ge2010 #ukelection #<PARTY>conservatives</PARTY></S> 
<S>@<PARTY>libdems</PARTY> check out this video of the #<PARTY>libdem</PARTY> flashmob <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> from #<PERSON>nickclegg</PERSON>sfault <URL>http://youtu.be/tO46i6OF90Q</URL> #iagreewith<PERSON>nick</PERSON> #ge2010</S> 
<S>Weird <ORGANIZATION>BBC</ORGANIZATION> news split screen <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> chatting with Paramedics on one side riot control in <LOCATION>Athens</LOCATION> on the other. <PERSON>Cam</PERSON> doing well #ge2010</S> 
<S>Interesting Q&amp;A in the #Guardian today, if you still have questions about who to vote for take a look at this: <URL>http://bit.ly/cBSf7p</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>My <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> general election quiz results at <URL>http://whoshouldyouvotefor.com</URL>: <PARTY>LAB</PARTY>+54 <PARTY>GRN</PARTY>+12 <PARTY>LIB</PARTY>+6 <URL>http://wsyvf.com/uk/6o2odBzIznQlpB9v</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @LonelyWonderer: <PERSON>Ben Bradshaw</PERSON>: nice guy, but he voted to introduce student tuition fees  #<LOCATION>Exeter</LOCATION> #ge2010</S>
<S>RT @jamesjdempsey: #imvoting<PARTY>labour</PARTY> because its about 61 million...not 3000 #ge2010</S> 
<S>#GE2010 now with Cam at an ambulance station in <LOCATION>Dudley</LOCATION>. V neck jumper has been junked for smart business suit</S> 
<S>#UKElection please! //Hashtag wars - will it be #ge2010  or #ukelection for tomorrow night? /via @benayers</S> 
<S>Vote for them or slap them - YOU decide <URL>http://dlvr.it/nSW7</URL>  #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>RT @majestic_whine: <PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> still campaigning and not sleeping. Interesting strategy for someone trying to shake cocaine rumours. #ge2010</S> 
<S><PERSON>Cameron</PERSON> still campaigning and not sleeping. Interesting strategy for someone still trying to shake cocaine rumours. #ge2010</S> 
<S>Pit stop for lunch at @plymouthlabour - who look after us very well indeed - then back on the #<PARTY>labour</PARTY>doorstep #ge2010</S>
<S>RT @LichfieldBlog: Meet the #<LOCATION>Lichfield</LOCATION> candidates: <PERSON>Michael Fabricant</PERSON> (<PARTY>Conservatives</PARTY>): <URL>http://ow.ly/1H89E</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @benarchibald: New blog post: With friends like these... <URL>http://nabidana.com/2010/05/05/with-friends-like-these/</URL> &lt;&lt;LOL.. #ge2010</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>I agreed most with <PERSON>Jim Barrie</PERSON> (<PARTY>Scottish National Party</PARTY>) in <LOCATION>Dundee West</LOCATION> - how about you? <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL> @democlub #ge2010 #<LOCATION>DundeeW</LOCATION></S> 
<S>New exclusive interviews with party spokespeople on volunteering @ivolunteeruk <URL>http://www.i-volunteer.org.uk/newshound/</URL> #ge2010</S> 
<S>3 tags tomorrow #ge2010 #ukelection #<PARTY>tory</PARTY>vision (<PARTY>Torys</PARTY> only) wouldnt want anyone to hurt themselves laughing at the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY></S> 
<S>The latest iPhone @myVoteApp opinion poll is: <PARTY>LIB</PARTY> 43%, <PARTY>CON</PARTY> 27%, <PARTY>LAB</PARTY> 18%, Others 4%. Your vote counts! #GE2010 <URL>http://bit.ly/d3jibQ</URL></S> 
<S>Would laugh if everyone backs a hung parliament at the bookies and votes <PARTY>lib dems</PARTY>, and then the <PARTY>lib dems</PARTY> get a shock majority. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @helenewilliams: Done second round of Socitm election survey of council websites - poor at promoting election date and voting #le2010 #ge2010 #localgovweb</S> 
<S><PERSON>William Hague</PERSON> Is the spitting image of <PERSON>John Locke</PERSON> from Lost #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @dominiccampbell: "You judge a party not by how it empowers the powerful, but how it supports the powerless" - <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> #ge2010 # ...</S> 
<S>4th most popular issue today: Community with 8.2% of the Vote. <URL>http://is.gd/bLmFP</URL> #leadersdebate #ge2010 #ukelection</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>RT @Paul_exp: I want a #noneoftheabove option on the ballot... #ge2010</S> 
<S>@dominiccampbell I agree. My pencil will be hovering over the  <PARTY>Labour</PARTY> box tomorrow, even though our MP has little to recommend him #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @UK_SPECTRE: Nigerians in the Home Office and Pakistanis in the Foreign Office  <URL>http://bit.ly/bwg2LI</URL>  #<PARTY>bnp</PARTY> #ge2010 #ukelection #elect ...</S> 
<S>RT @OpenRightsGroup: Demand disconnection powers are repealed: sign the petition! <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #deact #debill #ge2010</S> 
<S>If <PERSON>Brown</PERSON> stays we will be <LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION>. RT @JerryTaylor: Things could be worse, we could be <LOCATION>Greece</LOCATION> or the <PARTY>Tories</PARTY> could be in government. #ge2010</S> 
<S>RT @BradfordUni: A packed Atrium watches <PERSON>Gordon Brown</PERSON> speaking #ge2010 <URL>http://flic.kr/p/7YLm1H</URL></S> 
<S>@foxtailedgirl We will be watching it live here, so I really hope good stuff happens. Enjoy your train! #ge2010 #trainenvy</S> 
<S>I signed the petition to  repeal the Digital Economy Act <URL>http://bit.ly/deapetition</URL> #DEBill #DEAct #GE2010</S> 
<S>New WTWWM Post: What has #ge2010 taught us about marriage equality? <URL>http://bit.ly/9bjhBP</URL></S> 
<S>I agreed most with <PERSON>John Barnett</PERSON> (<PARTY>Liberal Democrats</PARTY>) in <LOCATION>Dundee West</LOCATION> - how about you? <URL>http://bit.ly/9MRs6t</URL> @democlub #ge2010 #<LOCATION>DundeeW</LOCATION></S> 
<S>@Stellaaahh Tactical voting means you vote for a party that you disagree with because our electoral system is broken #ge2010</S> 
<S>Where I live I have the power of 0.09 votes - no changes likely around here then! See your result at <URL>http://voterpower.org.uk</URL> #GE2010 #VPI</S> 
<S>RT @louise_ellman: #imnotvoting<PARTY>tory</PARTY> because I have a heart and actually care about society #ge2010 #ukelection #<PARTY>tory</PARTY> #<PARTY>libdems</PARTY> #<PARTY>labour</PARTY></S> 
